Guide to the United Mission to Nepal Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- A, Series I
  - Articles and papers
    - By UMN Personnel: A-11.03.01/0275- A-11.03.01/0316, 1993-1997 (Box 13, Folder 7-8)
      Including regarding: Helping the helpless; After the flood; Good Friday in Kathmandu; Making family out of foreigners; A different view,
    - By UMN Personnel: A-11.03.02, 1998-2000 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      Including regarding: UMN as I know it; What it's really about; A church service in Nepal
    - By Articles by UMN personnel on projects and Nepal/mission-related topics - (A-11.03), 1991-2005 (Box 188, Folder 5)
    - UMNers' Personal Circulars: A-11.04.01/0001- A11.04.01/0005, 1967-1983 (Box 13, Folder 9-10)
      Including regarding: Beth Bruneneir (1967-1973); Bob and Hazel Buckner (1971-1983), Joyce Brown (1975-1983); Bill Bridges (1981-1983); Valerie Collett (1966-1972)
    - UMNers' Personal Circulars: A-11.04.01/0006- A-11.04.01/0014, 1963-2005 (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
      Including regarding: John Cook (1963-1964); Mildred Drescher (1959-1962); Dick and Sue Harding (1979-); Norma Kehrberg (1970-1975); Jonathan and Evey Lindell (1956-1979), Margaret McCombe (1965-1986, 2005); Eileen Talbot (1974-1982); Tomako Tsukada (1967-1972), Betty Young (1974-)
    - UMNer's Circular letters: A-K, 1990s-2000s (Box 247)
    - UMNer's Circular letters: K-R, 1990s-2000s (Box 248)
    - UMNer's Circular letters: S-Z, 1990s-2000s (Box 249)
    - Articles and papers by others: including "A personal reflection on past missionary experience, focusing on the education of 'Third Culture Kids'..." by John Barclay; "The Social and Cultural Impacts of Tourism in Nepal" by Marian Burrows-Smith; "TEVT and Pro-Poor Development: Linkages - Past, Present, Future" by Larry C. Asher, 2001, 2003 (Box 253, Folder 15)
    - Visitors' Impressions: A-11.05.01/0001- A-11.05.01/0107, 1953-1999 (Box 14, Folder 4-7)
      Including: A glimpse into Nepal; Nepal on top of the world; Opportunity in Nepal; Road to Kathmandu; A dentist goes to Nepal, Butwal Technical Institute; The vision fulfilled; It began with a bird watcher; Nepal and the gospel of God; Taking time out to help
    - Newspapers articles on UMN in general - (A-11.06) (Newspaper reports on specific projects are with project; see also C-02), 1999-2004 (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - Audio-Visuals
    - Filmstrips: A-12.01.01/0001-0005: "Into Nepal Together" by E. Oliver and R. Ferger, black and white film strip with script; ""United Mission in Nepal", color, no script; "Himalayan Kingdom", color with script and tape; "Partnership in Nepal" and "Now in Nepal", produced by Church Missionary Society for their Children's Lenten Appeal, 1950s-1973 (Box 254)
    - VHS tapes: (A-12.01): "The Pipal Tree"; The First Fifteen Years; Uplifting Lives in Lalitpur; 1.Voice of Nepal, 2.NCF Program, 3. UMN/Sign Agreement; UMN TCSP Gorkha Project; Many Strings, One Chord; UMN 40th Anniversary Footage; Karivali Technical School; UMN Public Relations; NFE Jajarkot Village; Leather Goods (Box 234)
    - VHS tapes: (A-12.01): Nepal on the Move (The story of the UMN in Nepal. Produced by Interserve); Glimpses of HIStory in Nepal (An interview with Pastor Robert Karthak and UMN Archivist Betty Young); Our Life (with English caption); UJELI (English Subtitles); YWCA MELA 12-3-94; Uplifting Lives in Lalitpur; The Development Story EID; A Lengthy Privilege (Interview with Mrs Tullis Hofton); Press Confer. Dr. Helen Huston, Dec. 2, 1991 Journeying Together (A video presentation of the United Mission to Nepal's Health Services Department; Life More Abundant, The United mission to Nepal Celebrates its 50th anniversary (Box 235)
    - VHS tapes: (A-12.01): UMN 50th Celebration Activities; Life More Abundant: The United Mission to Nepal Celebrates its 50th anniversary; UMN Board Meeting May 2003; UMN 50th Anniversary Festival, May 24-26; Highlights of the Celebration of 50th Anniversary of UMN (Box 236)
    - Gramaphone records (A-12.02): two Church Missionary Society 45 rpm records, one United Methodist Church 33 1/3 rpm record, to be used with filmstrip "Himalayan Kingdom" (Box 254)
    - Cassette tapes: (A-12.02): Responsibility of Life; Audio-Visuals A.C. 2004 (May 24-25, 2004); Tapes on early discussions on [Dhanaj Hai?/Bulip?] (Box 246)
    - Calendars and notecards (A-12.03), 1975-2009 (Box 250, Folder 1)
    - Slide sets A-12.04.01/0001-0006: "Nepal and UMN by J. Lindell, 60 frames with script; "Happiness is Serving" (SBH Nursing School), 36 frames with script; "Greetings from Nepal" by H. Cronside, 50 frames with script; "Many Gifts One Spirit" by H. Cronside, 46 frames with script; "People and Mountains" by P. Stephens, 120 frames with tape; "Hills of Hope" by P. Stephens, 68 frames with script, "UMN Overview" by Tony McCall (A-12.04), 1960-1980s (Box 255)
    - Slides in boxes (A-12.05), including re. UMN Headquarters, Okhaldhunga, Mahendra Bhawan, Nursing School, Gorkha, Pokhara, Tansen hospital, Butwal, Visit of Queen Elizabeth II (1961) (Box 255)
    - Photographs (A-12.06): index - notebook with handwritten description of contents of UMN Photo Collection (Box 237)
    - Photographs: (A-12.06): Okhaldhunga; Gorkha; Shanta Bhawan; Patan Hospital; Tansen Palpa; Butwal (Box 237)
    - Photographs: (A-12.06): GBS Pokhara; Headquarters; Large UMN Photos; Nursing Campus Lalitpur; Mahendra Bhawan; Jumla; Set of UMN photos 1965 (Box 238)
    - Photographs: (A-12.06): HS Spares; Lamagara Photos; Nawal-Parasi; Official Meetings; Andhikhola, NRMP, Surkhet, Mental Health, Dandeldhura, Secondments, KISC Lalitpur, CDHP; Bhaktapur; Set of 100, 1962 Jajarkot (Box 239)
    - Photographs: (A-12.06): Patan Hosp. Building; Tansen Leprosy Work, Pedley (Box 240)
    - Photographs:(A-12.06): Pioneer Gorkha Photos (Box OV1)
    - Photographs: (A-12.06): Andhikhola, Butwal, Jhimruk, Khimti; Kathmandu Valley Health Services (Box 241)
    - Photographs: (A-12.06): Rural Development and Miscellaneous Programs; Gandaki Boarding School, Jajarkot, Jumla, KISC, Mahendra, Kath University, Bhawan (Box 242)
    - Photographs: (A-12.06): Pioneers,Okhaldunga, Tansen, Gorkha (Box 243)
    - Photographs: (A-12.06): Administration, Official Meetings, Enlargements 1965; Rural Development Department (Box 244)
    - Photographic negatives (Box 254)
    - Photographs and copies of documents gathered for historical display (Box 253, Folder 8)
    - Woodblock of "United Mission Headquarters Kathmandu" (Box 253, Folder 9)
  - American Friends Mission
    - Correspondence: A-13.00.01 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Assemblies of God
    - Correspondence: A-14.00.01 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Asianisation
    - Correspondence, reports: A-15.00.01/0001- A-15.00.01/0011 - RESTRICTED, 1958-1989 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Audits
    - Reports, minutes of Audit Committee: A-16.00.01/0001- A-16.00.01/0035 - RESTRICTED, 1962-1989 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Annual audited accounts, 1998-2004 (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - Archives
    - Archives: A-17.00.01/0001- A-17.00.01/0021 - RESTRICTED, 1968-1989 (Box 14, Folder 8-9)
      Including regarding: Correspondence by J. Lindell on establishing a museum in Nepal.; Need for a UMN archive collection: J. Lindell letter.; First circular requesting material by Betty Young; Proposal to move collection to UK, Script for "The First 15 Years" video.; Correspondence
    - Archives: A-17.00.01/0027- A-17.00.01/0047 - RESTRICTED, 1991-1999 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
      Including regarding: Reports; Archives dept. guidelines pamphlet; Annual plans; Memo on personnel files in archives, revised long term plan 1999/2002
    - Reports, etc. - (A-17.00) - RESTRICTED, 2001-2003 (Box 188, Folder 7)
    - Leaflets re. UMN archives, including ""Archives Department Guidelines", "The UMN Archives Collection and the CSCNWW" (Centre for the Study of Christianity in the Non-Western World, New College, Edinburgh), 1993, 2000, n.d. (Box 253, Folder 11)
- C, Series III
  - Children of UMNers
    - Hostel and Vehicle: C-01.01.01/0001- C-01.01.01/0047 - RESTRICTED, 1967-1986 (Box 38, Folder 1-5)
      Including regarding: Constitution; Policy on finances; Hostel fees and rules; Policy on finances; Annual reports
    - Education: General: C-01.02.01/0001- C-01.02.01/0108, 1969-1998 (Box 38, Folder 6-10)
      Including regarding: Educating the missionary child in Nepal; Minutes of EMC Committee; Schooling facilities for children of UMN workers; Home Schooling Newsletter No. 1
    - Education: General -Secondary Education of Expatriate Children: C-01.02.01/0042 (Box 163, Folder 1)
    - Education: General - Tutorial Group Record Book: C-01.02.01/0084 (Box 162, Folder 5)
    - Education: General: C-01.02.02/0001- C-01.02.02/0006, 1998 -1999 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      Including regarding: What are our goals as teachers of missionary children? Teachers' conference; Nepali staff children in TGS; Overview
    - Education: Kathmandu International Study Centre: C-01.03.01/0001- C-01.03.01/0137, 1963 -1994 (Box 39, Folder 2-6)
      Including regarding: Papers and correspondence on planning a school for Kathmandu; Alternative to boarding school for missionary children, Part I and Part II; Correspondence with INF; Circular appealing for funds
    - Education: Kathmandu International Study Centre (KISC): C-01.03.02/0001- C-01.03.02/0053, 1994-1999 (Box 39, Folder 7-10)
      Including regarding: Report by American parents; Long term development plan; KISC at risk; Handbook; Boarding report
    - Education: Kathmandu International Study Centre (KISC) C-01.03), 1998, 2000, 2004-2005 (Box 193, Folder 7)
    - Education: Kathmandu International Study Centre (KISC) C-01.03): Leaflet - "Introducing Saathi of KISC" (Box 252, Folder 12)
    - Education: Tutorial Groups - Andhikola and Butwal: C-01.04.01/0001- C-01.04.01/0002 - RESTRICTED, 1980-1999 (Box 40, Folder 1-3)
    - Education: Tutorial Groups - Gorkha: C-01.04.01/0003 - RESTRICTED, 1984 -1999 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Education: Tutorial Groups - Jakarkot, Jhimruk, Jumla: C-01.04.01/0004 - C-01.04.01/0006 - RESTRICTED, 1985-1997 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Education: Tutorial Groups - Kathmandu, Khimti, Okhaldhunga: C-01.04.02/0001 - C-01.04.02/0003 - RESTRICTED, 1989-1997 (Box 40, Folder 6-7)
      Including regarding: Kathmandu: Information sheet; Annual report; AGM; General information; Khimti: Annual report; Okhaldhunga: Annual reports; Reports
    - Education: Tutorial Groups - Pkhara, Surkhet, Tansen: C-01.04.02/0004 - C-01.04.02/0006 - RESTRICTED, 1973- 2000 (Box 40, Folder 8-9)
    - Education: Tutorial Groups and children's education general C-01.04), 2000-2005 (Box 193, Folder 8)
    - Education: Tutorial Groups: Butwal, Tansen C-01.04), 2002-2005 (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - Education: Tutorial Groups: Kathmandu (closed 2006) C-01.04), 2000-2006 (Box 193, Folder 10)
    - Education: Schools for Nepali Staff Children: C-01.05.01/0001 - C-01.05.01/0017, 1985-1997 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Education: KISC Correspondence: C-01.06.01/0001 - C-01.06.01/0014 - RESTRICTED, 1984-1998 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Christian Witness/ Church Relationship
    - Correspondence, reports, etc.: C-02.00.01/0001 - C-02.00.01/0131 - RESTRICTED, 1959 -1992 (Box 41, Folder 1-4)
      Including regarding: Report of conversation in HMG offices; Regarding mission's relation with church; Some thoughts regarding mission in Nepal; The Christian and the Law of Nepal; Declaration of human rights
    - Correspondence, reports, etc.: C-02.00.02/0001 - C-02.00.02/0055 - RESTRICTED, 1992 -1999 (Box 41, Folder 5-8)
      Including regarding: NCFN presentation in UK; UMN's role in the ministry of the church in Nepal; UMN and Christian Witness in Nepal; Letter to Focus Committee
    - General (C-02.00) - RESTRICTED, 1998-2000 (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Press cuttings and petition against UMN (C-02.00) - RESTRICTED, 1999-2002 (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - Coordinating Committee
    - Minutes: C-03.00.04 - RESTRICTED, 2001 Jan- 2002 Mar (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Minutes: C-03.00.04 - RESTRICTED, 2002 Apr- 2007 Mar (Box 42, Folder 1-2)
    - Minutes: C-03.00) - RESTRICTED, 2000- 2001 Jul (Box 194, Folder 4-6)
    - Minutes: C-03.00) - RESTRICTED, 2001 Aug-2003 Jun (Box 195, Folder 1-3)
    - Leadership Team (replaced Coordinating Committee) - Minutes C-03/02) - RESTRICTED, 2003 Jun - 2004 (Box 195, Folder 4-5)
  - Consultations with Member Bodies by Executive Director
    - Minutes and reports of consultations in USA; Australia; Europe; Far East: C-04.00.01/0001 - C-04.00.01/0020 - RESTRICTED, 1964-1995 (Box 42, Folder 3-5)
  - Culture Study
    - Culture Study Committee, small group discussions, papers by UMNers: C-05.00.01/0001 - C-05.00.01/0024, 1975-1992, n.d. (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Papers by Non-UMNers; Culture library, Cultural practices and adjustments: C-05.00.01/0025 - C-05.00.01/0055, 1975-1980 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      Including regarding Nepali religious ceremonies, evil spirits, nutrition, traditional health beliefs, behavior and dress, observed customs
  - Constitution and By-Laws of UMN
    - Constitution and By-Laws of UMN: C-06.00.01/0001 - C-06.00.01/0015 - RESTRICTED, 1956 - 2002 (Box 43, Folder 1-4)
      Including regarding: Correspondence and drafts leading up to approved Constitution and By laws, minutes of Continuation Committee
    - Discussion and approved docs (C-06.00)- RESTRICTED, 2001-2007 (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - Other C
    - Church of Scotland: C-07.00.01, 1954- 1990 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Church of North India/ UCNI: C-08.00.01, 1954- 2001 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Church of South India; C.M.S. Australia ;Church Missionary Society, Ireland, Church Missionary Society, UK.: C-09.00.01, C-10.00.01, C-11.00.01, C-12.00.01, 1957-2001 (Box 43, Folder 7-8)
    - Committee for Service Overseas, Germany (DU): C-13.00.01, 1961 - 2001 (Box 43, Folder 9-10)
    - Common Global Ministries Board/ UCMS/ Christian Church (Disciples): C-14.00.01, 1955- 2006 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Christian Medical Commission: C-15.00.01, 1971-1982 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Christian Service Corporations, CODEL: C-16.00.01, C-17.00.01, 1973 -1987 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Conference of Missionary Societies in Great Britain and Ireland, Calendars: C-18.00.01, C-19.00.01, 1954 - 2001 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Commission of European Communities: C-20.00.01, 1978-1979 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Central Asian Mission: C-21.00.01, 1955-1961 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Central Agency (EZE),: C-22.00.01 - RESTRICTED, 1976 -1996 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Computers: C-23.00.01/0001 - C-23.00.01/0053, 1983-1998 (Box 44, Folder 7-9)
      Including regarding: Nepal and micro-computers; David Matthew's correspondence; User's Needs Group agenda only; Business School computers; UMN computer systems
    - Canadian International Development Agency (CIDA): C-24.00.01 - RESTRICTED, 1974-1980 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Christoffel Blinden Mission: C-25.00.01 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Christian Conference of Asia: C-26.00.01 - RESTRICTED, 1959-1990 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Charts and Consolidated Records: C-27.00.01, 1954-1993 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      Including regarding: Member body records with personnel and grants each year; Chart of member body membership each year; Chart of projects undertaken each year with detailed historical file
  - CD ROMs: C-28.00.01
    - Photographs: C-28.00.01, 2000 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      Nearly 850 photographs covering UMN's history: listing and some photos
    - UMN Document archive: C-28.00.01, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 2)
      Set of 5 CDs for public distribution: full listing of contents of each CD ROM - listing on CD ROM 5
    - UMN CDs: C-28.00.01 - RESTRICTED, 2001 (Box 45, Folder 3-4)
      Set of 7 CDs for UMN use only, including the Document Archive CD material and extra papers.(Contents list on each CD); One CD of Confidential material; Database CD
    - CDs: (C-028): UMN Strategic Plan 2003-2008; A Time to Grow; Butternorth—Weekly Updates 2002-2004; UMN Publications 2004-2005; Various documents around 2000 (incl. hardcopy index) —Administration, Education, Health Services, Industrial development, Rural development; UMN Nov. Board meeting minute & attachments (2003, 2004, 2005); General Assembly 2005 minutes and minute appendices; Presentation to the General Assembly April 2005; Annual Conf 2002, Jennie Collins Sessions; Leadership Team Meetings Papers, Notes, and Minutes, July 2003-2006; Board and General Assembly Meeting; Papers and Minutes, Nov. 2003-2006; UMN's Local Partners; Maya reaching out with love; A time to grow; Forgiveness and reconciliation; Fifty years in God's hand, UMN 1954-2004; Hurdles, why we hope; History of UMN and Nepali Church, B. Young, Feb. 2001 (Box 245)
    - CDs: (C-028): UMN History Backup (Box 251)
- D, Series IV
  - Danish Santal Mission
    - Correspondence: D-01.00.01, 1981-2004 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Disaster Relief / Preparedness Programme
    - General: D-02.00.01/0001 - D-02.00.01/0011, 1966 Jul- 1981 Oct (Box 46, Folder 1)
      Including regarding: Correspondence on earthquake in West Nepal; Floods in Butwal area; Floods in mid-West
    - General: D-02.00.01/0012 - D-02.00.01/0020, 1982 Feb- 1987 Aug (Box 46, Folder 2)
      Including regarding: Policies concerning relief work, quoting minutes of Board and IDC; Emergencies: Relief work committee of IDC; Relief request regarding burned house in Lalitpur; Food scarcity criteria and reporting system
    - General: D-02.00.01/0021 - D-02.00.01/0033, 1988 Jul- 1994 Dec (Box 46, Folder 3)
      Including regarding: Use of disaster fund for boundary wall refused; Victims of democracy riots; Floods in Butwal; Emergency procedures in UMN; Mental health aspects of disaster management
    - General: D-02.00.01/0034 - D-02.00.01/0041, 1995 Apr-1996 (Box 46, Folder 4)
      Including regarding: Castastrophic urban disaster management; Mini workshop; Funding request; Meeting minutes; Disaster management
    - General: D-02.00.01/0042 - D-02.00.01/0052, 1996 Nov- 1997 Sep (Box 46, Folder 5)
      Including regarding: Report on disaster management course; Some suggestions for earthquake preparedness; Society for earthquake technology of Nepal; Trauma counselling workshop, details and report
    - General: D-02.00.01/0053 - D-02.00.01/0065, 1998-1998 Aug (Box 46, Folder 6)
      Biographical / Historical
      Including regarding: Disaster management in Nepal; Health medical consequences of earthquakes; Disaster preparedness workshop; First progress report of ERH Project; Agreement with National Society for Earthquake Technology, Nepal
    - General: D-02.00.01/0066 - D-02.00.01/0069, 1999 Jan-Dec (Box 46, Folder 7)
      Including regarding: Earthquake safety day program; Disaster response program; Earthquake resistant houses in Nepal - leaflet
    - General: plans, reports, etc. (D-02.01), 1999-2005 (Box 197, Folder 1-2)
    - Earthquake: D-02.02.01, 1988 Jul (Box 46, Folder 8-9)
      Including regarding: File of reports, circulars, etc. on earthquake
    - Earthquake: D-02.02.01/29, D-02.02.01/30, 1988 (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Floods: D-02.03.01, 1993 Jul (Box 46, Folder 10)
      Including regarding: File of reports, etc. on major flooding disaster in Central Nepal
    - Triagency: D-02.04.01/0001 - D-02.04.01/0028, 1988 - 1999 (Box 46, Folder 11-13)
      Including regarding: Minutes and meeting; Sub-Himalayan inter-relatedness; Papers presented to consultation; Constraints regarding disasters, UMN; CASA disaster response
    - Tri-agency / Regional Inter-Agency Programme (RIAP) (D-02.04), 1995-2000 (Box 197, Folder 3)
  - Death Disposal
    - Correspondence on burial and cremation; UMN death forms: D-03.00.01, 1965-1993 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Dandeldhura
    - Correspondence, etc.: D-04.00.01/0001 - D-04.00.01/0021, 1958-1970 (Box 45, Folder 9-10)
      Including regarding: Correspondence with Kate Young; Initial plans and arrangements; Correspondence regarding building; Report on work
  - Materials Development Program
    - Re. literacy materials: D-05.00.01/0001 - D-05.00.01/0011, 1976-1985 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      Including regarding: Correspondence regarding literacy materials; UMN materials development; Circulars to encourage writing of materials; Circulars regarding material available, needs and production
    - Re. literacy materials: D-05.00.01 (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Development Communication Productions
    - Development Communication Productions: D-05.00.01/0012 - D-05.00.01/0089, 1986 -1995 (Box 47, Folder 2-6)
      Including regarding: minutes; materials produced by DCP; planning
    - Development Communication Productions -Catalogue: D-05.00.01/0090, 1999 (Box 163, Folder 3)
    - Development Communication Productions - Communications Office Brochure and Catalogue: D-05.00.01/92, 2000 (Box 166, Folder 4)
    - Development Communication Productions - Reports, etc. (D-05.00), 1993-2002 (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Development Communication Productions - leaflet (D-05.00), n.d. (Box 252, Folder 14)
  - Dhading (NCFN - HDCS)
    See Nepal Church History Project for more material on HDCS.
    - Correspondence, reports, etc.: D-06.00.01/0001 - D-06.00.01/0035, 1991-2000 (Box 45, Folder 5-6)
    - Correspondence, reports, etc. - Annual report S. Ranjit-06.00.01/0021, 1992 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, reports, etc. -Needs Analysis Report: D-06.00.01/0033, 1997 (Box 167, Folder 2)
    - Dhading - appeal leaflet, n.d. (Box 252, Folder 10)
  - Dullu
    - Correspondence, reports, etc.: D-07.01.01/0001 - D-07.01.01/0035, 1995 - 2000 (Box 47, Folder 7-8)
      Including regarding: Site visit report; Work plans; Contract with local officials; Informal report; Summary and detailed annual reports; Visit report; Circular letter; Practice teaching report
    - Dulllu School Partnership Programme - plans, reports, etc. (closed, Maoist threat) (D-07.01), 1995-2004 (Box 197, Folder 5)
  - Dailekh Project
    - Correspondence, reports, etc.: D-08.01.01/0000 - D-08.01.01/0025, 1997- 1999 (Box 47, Folder 9-10)
      Including regarding: Baseline survey; Project description; Strategic plan; Annual plan; Planning meetings; Agreement with HMG; Quarterly report
    - Dailekh Non-Formal Education Programme - reports, plans, etc. (closed, Maoist threat) (D-08.01), 1999-2004 (Box 197, Folder 6)
- B, Series II
  - Bhaktapur Hospital
    - B-01.00.01/0001- B-01.00.01/0067 - RESTRICTED, 1954-1975 (Box 15, Folder 3-6)
    - B-01.00.01/0070- B-01.00.01/0072 - RESTRICTED, 1963-1973 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Including regarding: Record of general staff meetings 1963-1973; Drawing plans; Visitors' book
  - Board of Directors, Executive and Finance Committees, General Assembly Meetings
    Agendas, notes, and correspondence in these files. Minutes are printed in bound books; see B-02.02; Agenda papers transferred to subject files: projects, personnel, employment, business/finance, planning and structure, etc.
    - Meeting files: B-02.00.01 - RESTRICTED, 1953-1969 (Box 15, Folder 8-9)
    - Meeting files: B-02.00.01 - RESTRICTED, 1969-1999 (Box 16, Folder 1-10)
    - Meeting files (B-02.01) - RESTRICTED, 2001-2004 (Box 188, Folder 8)
    - Board, Full agenda papers, May 2003 (B-02.01) - RESTRICTED (Box 189, Folder 1)
    - Board, Full agenda papers, May, November 2004 (B-02.01) - RESTRICTED (Box 189, Folder 2)
    - Agendas: Board and General Assembly -(B-02.01) - RESTRICTED, 2005 (Box 189, Folder 3)
    - Bound volumes of minutes, 1954-1972 (Box 174)
    - Bound volumes of minutes, 1973-1981 (Box 175)
    - Bound volumes of minutes, 1981-1984 (Box 176)
    - Bound volumes of minutes, 1985-1987 (Box 177)
    - Bound volumes of minutes, 1988-1990 (Box 178)
    - Bound volumes of minutes, 1991-1993 (Box 179)
    - Bound volumes of minutes, 1994-1997 (Box 180)
    - Bound volumes of minutes, 1998-1999 (Box 181)
    - Bound volumes of minutes, 2000-2002 (Box 182)
    - Bound volumes of minutes, 2003-2004 (Box 183)